<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Orn Smith&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Orn Smith&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Orn Smith&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/img/about-orn.jpg</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/img/about-orn.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.133.1</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the AI Governance Landscape: The Players and the Missing Pieces</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/ai-governace-players-gaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/ai-governace-players-gaps/</guid>
      <description>Over the past 5-6 months, I’ve been diving deep into the world of AI alignment and governance. Given my background as a go-to-market practitioner and my interest in advocacy, I’m particularly fascinated by how this field is becoming more accessible, especially within the private sector. This article is my wrap-up of the research I’ve done so far, along with some thoughts on where the gaps lie in the current AI governance landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for visiting and sorry my blog in English looks pretty empty here. This blog is still in progress. I&amp;rsquo;m in the middle of migrating from my old site, editing and transferring my content here. Please stay tune!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect with me at:
LinkedIn Contact: osmithip[at]alumni.cmu.edu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! 👋 Glad to see you&amp;rsquo;re interested in hearing more about me! This page is kinda long as I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to reflect on who I am and who I want to be.
Who am I? When I write online, I go by the pen name Orn Smith. I&amp;rsquo;m a writer, educator, and entrepreneur driven to make a positive impact. I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated my career to empowering individuals and shaping industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing &amp; Training</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/training-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/training-marketing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m passionate in educational design, capacity building and helping individuals and organizations grow. My specialization is in Inbound Marketing and related fields.
Inbound Marketing (Digital Marketing Strategy)
Inbound Marketing is a set of proven marketing strategies that brings together branding, content marketing, first-party data collection, and marketing technology. It’s been a secret sauce of how I acquired and retain customers of my businesses, as well as providing the service to my clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture Building</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/product-venture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/product-venture/</guid>
      <description>As a seasoned entrepreneur, I&amp;rsquo;ve played a pivotal role in the founding and growth of several successful ventures across diverse industries. My portfolio includes experiences in media &amp;amp; publication, education, digital marketing services, and e-commerce products.
One of my most notable accomplishments is the development of &amp;ldquo;Content Shifu,&amp;rdquo; a leading digital marketing media, education, and ecosystem builder. From its inception, I spearheaded its growth into a thriving company that has established a strong presence in the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/portfolio/overview/</guid>
      <description>A passionate professional with experience at the intersection of entrepreneurship, marketing, education and social innovation.
I recently completed a Master degree in Public Policy &amp;amp; Management at Carnegie Mellon University.
Prior to that, I have 10 years of experience in the online content and marketing industries, as well as 7+ years as an entrepreneur, consultant and educator and have educated over 3,000 professionals.
Skills and Experience
Product discovery and venture building read more about them Strategic Marketing and Consulting Event &amp;amp; media relations Education &amp;amp; Community Empowerment Responsible Technology &amp;amp; Policy This page is still a work in progress Want to explore more or see more details?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What am I up to now?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/now/</guid>
      <description>Work &amp;amp; Projects 💼 Open for work: exploring new opportunities particularly in the field of Responsible Technology and Responsible AI 👩🏻‍🏫 Training and Seminar design projects for a few clients 💡 Exploring some social innovation ideas Learning / Mastering 💻 AI Alignment &amp;amp; AI Safety (Just Completed) 🤝 Participating: Academy of Changemakers Excellence 📖 Taking course: Applied Behavioral Science Masterclass, More of AI 📚 Reading: Psychology of Money, Gamification (Just Completed) 💻 Revamping this personal website!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
